import 'package:e_learning/model/quiz_data.dart';

final List<QuizData> quiz1 = [
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Toothpaste",
    options: ["Personal Computer", "Luxury car", "Toothpaste", "Refrigerator"],
    question: "Which of the following is an example of an FMCG product? ",
  ),
  const QuizData(
      answer: "Rapid sales turnover",
      options: [
        "Long shelf life",
        "Slow sales turnover",
        "Rapid sales turnover",
        "High-cost manufacturing"
      ],
      question: "FMCG products are known for?"),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "High involvement purchase",
    options: [
      "Low involvement purchase",
      "Routine purchase",
      "High involvement purchase",
      "Impulse purchase"
    ],
    question: "Buying a house or a car is an example of?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Personal relevance and importance",
    options: [
      "Price alone",
      "Personal relevance and importance",
      "Brand popularity",
      "Sales promotions"
    ],
    question:
        "In the context of consumer behavior, the level of involvement is influenced by",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Habit and routine",
    options: [
      "Extensive research",
      "Emotional connections",
      "Brand loyalty",
      "Habit and routine"
    ],
    question:
        "For low involvement products, consumers are more likely to rely on",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Impulse purchase",
    options: [
      "High involvement purchase",
      "Impulse purchase",
      "Complex decision-making process",
      "Extended problem-solving purchase"
    ],
    question:
        "Buying a cup of coffee or a snack from a vending machine is an example of?",
  ),
];

final List<QuizData> quiz2 = [
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Ansoff Matrix",
    options: [
      "BCG Matrix",
      "SWOT Analysis",
      "PESTLE Analysis",
      "Ansoff Matrix"
    ],
    question:
        "Market Penetration, Market Development, Product Development, and Diversification are growth strategies commonly associated with which matrix used in marketing strategy?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Transporting products from manufacturer to consumer",
    options: [
      "Managing customer relationships",
      "Transporting products from manufacturer to consumer",
      "Generating advertising campaigns",
      "Conducting market research"
    ],
    question: "What is a key function of a Distribution Channel?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Utilizing electronic point-of-sale systems",
    options: [
      "Conducting surveys with consumers",
      "Observing employee behavior",
      "Utilizing electronic point-of-sale systems",
      "Analyzing weather patterns"
    ],
    question: "How does Nielsen RMS typically collect sales data?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "The relative importance of each store based on its sales volume",
    options: [
      "The weight of each product in terms of physical mass",
      "The relative importance of each store based on its sales volume",
      "The distribution of products based on their packaging weight",
      "The total weight of products sold in a specific category"
    ],
    question: "Weighted Distribution in Nielsen RMS takes into account:",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Indirect Distribution",
    options: [
      "Direct-to-Consumer (DTC)",
      "Omnichannel Distribution",
      "Indirect Distribution",
      "E-commerce Distribution"
    ],
    question:
        "Which distribution channel is commonly used for FMCG products, involving multiple intermediaries such as wholesalers and retailers?",
  ),
];

final List<QuizData> quiz3 = [
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Building long-term brand loyalty",
    options: [
      "Building long-term brand loyalty",
      "Targeting niche markets",
      "Achieving one-time sales spikes",
      "Minimizing brand visibility"
    ],
    question: "What is the primary goal of FMCG advertising and promotions?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Providing entertainment in retail stores to attract customers",
    options: [
      "Offering discounts on retail products",
      "Providing entertainment in retail stores to attract customers",
      "Exclusively selling entertainment products",
      "Receiving training in retail management"
    ],
    question: "What is the concept of 'retail-tainment' in merchandising?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Point of Purchase",
    options: [
      "Price of Products",
      "Point of Purchase",
      "Promotion of Products",
      "Place of Purchase"
    ],
    question: "What does POP stand for in the context of retail?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Cash registers and checkout areas",
    options: [
      "Displays showcasing products",
      "Cash registers and checkout areas",
      "Marketing promotions in-store",
      "Product demonstration booths"
    ],
    question:
        "Which of the following best describes Point of Sale (POS) systems?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "To optimize product placement on shelves",
    options: [
      "To organize staff schedules",
      "To create visual displays in-store",
      "To manage inventory levels",
      "To optimize product placement on shelves"
    ],
    question: "What is the purpose of a planogram in merchandising?",
  ),
];

final List<QuizData> quizDataList1 = [
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Hair Dryer",
    options: [
      "Hair Dryer",
      "Hair Shampoo",
      "Hair Conditioner",
      "Detergent",
    ],
    question: "1. Which one of the below is NOT an example for FMCG?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Painkiller",
    options: [
      "Painkiller",
      "Shampoo",
      "Toilet Paper",
      "Toaster",
    ],
    question:
        "2. Which one of the below is NOT an example for a Low Involvement Product?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Information Search",
    options: [
      "Package Design",
      "Trigger to purchase",
      "Information Search",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    question:
        "3. Which one of the below is a step involved in the purchase of a High Involvement Product?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Complex Buying Behaviour",
    options: [
      "Complex Buying Behaviour",
      "Variety Seeking Behaviour",
      "Habitual Buying Behaviour",
      "Dissonance Reducing Buying Behaviour",
    ],
    question:
        "4. Which of the cases best describes High Involvement and Significant difference between brands?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer:
        "Distribution involves the physical movement and transfer of goods from the manufacturer to the end consumer.",
    options: [
      "Distribution refers to the process of manufacturing a product.",
      "Distribution involves the physical movement and transfer of goods from the manufacturer to the end consumer.",
      "Distribution is the promotion of products through advertising and marketing channels.",
      "Distribution signifies the pricing strategy employed for selling products in the market.",
    ],
    question: "5. What is Distribution?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Limited market coverage",
    options: [
      "The competition will be higher",
      "Limited market coverage",
      "Both A & B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    question:
        "6. What is a disadvantage of Indirect Distribution when compared to Direct Distribution?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Kirana Stores",
      "Super Market",
      "Cosmetic store",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    question: "7. Which is the best outlet type to sell shampoo sachets?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Margin provided on the product",
      "Fill rate",
      "Credit provided",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    question:
        "8. What are some of the factors that affect Channel Satisfaction?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer:
        "Promotion of the sale of goods that can employ pricing, special offer, display, & other techniques",
    options: [
      "Promotion of the sale of goods that can employ pricing, special offer, display, & other techniques",
      "Choosing the name of the brand in such a way that the products can be sold to the consumers",
      "Selling products in an unbranded format to the consumers without giving any special offer, display & technique",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    question: "9. What is the meaning of the term 'Merchandising'?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "To influence the shopper into purchasing the product",
    options: [
      "To influence the shopper into purchasing the product",
      "To capture the attention of the shopper",
      "Both A & B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    question: "10. What is the purpose of using a Point of Purchase Display?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Eye Level",
    options: [
      "Eye Level",
      "In top most shelf",
      "In the bottom most shelf",
      "The placement of product has 0 influence on the purchase",
    ],
    question:
        "11. If you want a higher probability of selling the product, where should the product be placed?",
  ),
  const QuizData(
    answer: "Products that are seen as soon as someone enters the shop",
    options: [
      "Products that are kept at the eye level",
      "Products that are seen as soon as someone enters the shop",
      "Products that kept along with other products of the same category",
      "Products that are not seen in the first glance",
    ],
    question: "12. What is meant by Primary Visibility?",
  ),
];
